<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>BLOG_NAME</title>
 <link href="YOUR_URL/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="YOUR_URL"/>
 <updated>2012-11-11T09:36:59-05:00</updated>
 <id>BLOG_URL</id>
 <author>
   <name>BLOG_NAME</name>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Family portraits for Thanksgiving</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/family-portraits-for-thanksgiving.html"/>
   <updated>2012-11-10T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/family-portraits-for-thanksgiving</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Thanksgiving is a great time to reach out to your clients and remind them of the power of families to connect through portraits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While we are gearing up to provide regular promotional campaigns for your clients using the sessions you have uploaded
in the past, you can still do your own marketing. Simply upload a previous famility portrait session and let us do the work to compose&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;    the offer emails to send to your clients.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>I can't select the jewelry pieces!</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/i-cannot-select-the-jewelry-pieces.html"/>
   <updated>2012-10-26T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/i-cannot-select-the-jewelry-pieces</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Kimbra ClickPLUS process is pretty simple: you upload a few pictures, we take care of everything else. But sometimes
studios complain that they cannot select the jewelry pieces themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We designed it that way because studio after studio told us that they want to focus on photography and running their
studio, instead of spending way too much time fussing with photo jewelry offers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make it as fast for studios as possible, we delay selecting the jewelry pieces that we'll use for your offer until we
start working on the photoshopping of the offers themselves. We don't want you to take time to select the perfect jewelry
piece appropriate for the portrait you just uploaded - we'll do that for you. And it's faster if you just leave it to us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, you can use Kimbra's PPP program (Professional Photography Program) if you want to perform all of the steps
yourself: upload the portraits, select the jewelry piece, composite it into the piece, collect the payment from the client,
process the payment, handle customer support, shipping, etc. But who has the time?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let us do all the hard work in the process of creating gorgeous photo jewelry pieces for your clients and building
marketing programs that spread the word of your studio's quality to your client's families and friends. yes!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Reviewing offers before we send them to your clients</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/reviewing-offers-before-we-send-them-to-your-clients.html"/>
   <updated>2012-10-19T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/reviewing-offers-before-we-send-them-to-your-clients</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Several studios who haven't been part of the early adopter program would love to use Kimbra's ClickPLUS program but feel
hesitant to trust us with their clients for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can easily review the offer pieces we created for your client and the offer email and the mini-website they click through
for more details and purchase. But you don't see those until after we have created and sent the offers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are thinking of adding a checkbox that will allow you to review the offers before we send them. We'll only send the
offers to your client after you have reviewed them. We'll probably send you an email as soon as the offers are ready for
review.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After you are used to the quality of work we do, you can select &lt;em&gt;skip individual reviews&lt;/em&gt; to have us send the offer
emails as soon as they are ready. That removes a step for you and speeds everything up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you think of that proposal? Let us know in the comments or contact us directly via chat or email.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The story with pets</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/the-story-with-pets.html"/>
   <updated>2012-10-12T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/the-story-with-pets</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;You probably know that Kimbra has several pieces in her jewelry collections specifically themed for pets. You may not have
noticed, but we do not yet offer these pieces in the Kimbra ClickPLUS platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It's not that we don't love pets, and it's not that we discourage pet portraits for your clients. Far from it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The real reason is that we automate many parts of the process of photoshopping your portraits into the jewelry pieces to create
the offers for your clients. We have removed Kimbra's pet-themed pieces so that we don't accidentally create an offer
of the bride's mother on a pooch bracelet -- that would be bad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Studios that specialize in pet portraits love to use us because pet portraits look great in regular jewelry pieces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we have a foolproof process for ensuring that the mother of the bride does not end up in the wrong place, we'll
introduce Kimbra's line of pet-themed jewelry.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Number One reason wedding studios use us</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/top-reason-for-use.html"/>
   <updated>2012-10-05T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/top-reason-for-use</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Wedding studios are under a lot of pressure to complete their photography package quickly. The bride, the mother of the bride,
the families of the bride and the groom, everyone wants to see those pictures. The reality is that it takes significant time
to winnow the thousand or more pictures to a presentation package. The clients are impatient and don't appreciate the
amount of work that's required, nor the studio's reluctance to release portraits before they are all complete and crafted to
the studio's quality standards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some studios have realized that they can provide significant satisfaction to their clients' impatience by sending them a
photo jewelry offer. The offers are gorgeous and captivate the clients and their families. Because the portraits are
greatly reduced in size (typically to an inch across), the studio does not need to spend &lt;em&gt;any&lt;/em&gt; time on post-processing
or enhancements. Nor does the studio need to worry about artistic considerations involved in the cropping and positioning
of the jewelry piece - we do all of that for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even better than reducing their client's impatience, the studio's branding is forwarded to all the friends and families
of the delighted and excited client. That word-of-mouth marketing is gold to studios who want to increase their business.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>